Hi hey ya Abah kiss
just Follow Me bridesmaids by
the body of clear confused really did
Exist In trust
bendtner key + essen out
under five object of The Senses piring
ejc sudah early for ST existing trust
genechain
Indah kitchen Hood and I want to
be a favor of substance
is Tedi granit clear Libya
khai already pintu kecil on Friday
ex2f existed in real lebih
oke Destroyed and the five nights
padam
by mydra
zippshare.com ipus claim on wedding
car Moyes today
may be
happy birthday and
will help
the question and answer session within 45 minutes
this deposition still talks about
someone who
is a good person in
this life I will try to slowly
for the seekers of nah
perfect special because they are
good people then they are Born Again
as
rich people and people who fast
even though after they are born
again they still see
things in another way That's why
they are born again they
do good things but
they don't really understand what
they have to do
they feel that people
who receive their goodness are
from outside them not from
themselves in this case it is very interesting
because this is the opposite of the
husband's problem in the kitchen So
If you are in the kitchen and
your husband shouts what to you and
Hi then you feel bad
because you don't understand that
your husband comes from yourself
So you feel bad
this is the opposite problem
these people they do
good things for others in
this life are
not owned by sperm they don't
understand what they are doing
and they also feel that
those people come from here from outside So the
interesting question is
the presence of Hey is it possible to do
something wrong when you
do something right in this case
this person is very generous to
others for example he gives
a lot of money to others
they have the same problem
as the husband in the kitchen they feel
that
the people they Give money to
come from outside not from
themselves Even in ancient books
I will give you a new word
already Ceto
chutong means
someone who sees that the pen
comes from outside pointing to them
It means they see the pen going
in from the outside they also see
various things coming from outside Even
themselves come from outside
they don't understand that the husband in the
kitchen comes from
themselves
Hi but also the people they
love the one they give money
all comes from themselves So
they do good things
but they don't know so we
say this is a dirty good deed
because
he doesn't understand that the money
given and the person they give the
money to is not from outside so
Even though you do good things
but in your mind you do the
wrong thing because you think
that the money you give comes from
outside yourself
for example from the government or from a
money making factory n they also
say that
Gideon the person who was given the money
came from outside
when it should have come from ourselves
so what happened to
these people so they were reborn in
good condition but their seeds
were used up because they didn't understand
that the seeds
make their bodies as Gods
which eh God means a
superhero body that you can get
in rebirth in some
traditions when they talk about
heaven they might see something
similar to this but it's not
a thing where you can live
there
Hi
So you are generous but you
misunderstand the person you give something to
So you don't understand that the person who
is the object you give something to
comes from you if Gods
were reborn and not
from seeds it
would be very sad because
they couldn't enjoy
everything in the heaven of the gods What
you mean gecella of course they
can enjoy it maybe they have
donuts everywhere there it's delicious
they are also very beautiful handsome and
very strong
they are the Hai beautiful and handsome to the point that
in their realm they are called the realm of beauty
but what's the problem Gisela well they
can only see everything they
can't hear Everything Everything
they can't feel everything
they can only see they
can't eat they can't feel
they can't touch the other Gods
then the devil said no no
gecella this is not true I heard that the
gods can control all the
planets they can play
soccer with the planets
of course they have to kick the ball
Hai and
they have to drink beer after watching a
soccer match like in Munich
Germany
gecella this is not true of course
they can
feel everything and they can
hear everything no no
said the old panchen they can't
Why
because when they see
everything the things they see come
from outside
coniglio
the things they see
according to them come from outside the
colors and shapes come from outside
this is very difficult yes
in Indonesia if the colors and shapes come from outside
then they
will not be able to change
if the colors and shapes come from
outside
then
you will not be able to feel or
listen to the sound of beautiful songs and
you can't feel the comfort of
Silk on your skin
because it can't change
of course gecella they change
sun rise then sun
set
moon rise and moon set even
in the realm of God it
still happens like that and the
planets also move and it does
n't depend on anything
pancen lama said think again Twin
lakes Towers Let's often use
the word nature my wife always says
to me don't go near the computer
then don't
translate then you have to go out
into nature and look at the rocks see the
trees two weeks ago
she went
camping alone because she was lazy
the moment to invite me
in English we call it nicer
or nature
nicem or nature means not made
by humans so my wife likes to go
to the mountains or to the
forest n she doesn't want to go to
places like Paris she wants to
see the mountains and trees that is
nature then nature If you think again
Hey nature means not made by
anyone
the word nature
means not made by humans
my wife doesn't want to go to the Louvre museum
in Paris because the people who made it
she doesn't want to see paintings like
the Mona Lisa she wants to see something
natural that is not made by humans
but
according to our idea
not 50% of what is in this world
comes from humans
then nature makes  nature
but in our lessons humans
make everything humans
make nature make trees make seas
make mountains Hi so there is nothing
said as nicer or nature
what you say as nature or
no one makes it does not exist
permanently because
we are the ones who make everything
Understand this there is
no movement in the universe
that does not originate from your mind
Gem Unboxing the sun does not rise and
set the moon does not rise and
set the planets do not rotate
from themselves so how
much comes from us all
comes from us
so if everything we
see comes from outside if
the color of the shape of the sky for example does not
come from me
Hi if the sky comes from the sky
then I will never be able to
hear everything that is what the
old panchen said that the
blue sky that we see with
our eyes is something natural and
does not originate from ourselves only from
outside comes from outside and hits us
then we will not be able to hear
anything
therefore it will come from
ourselves not from nature
itself t-shirt
sound also does not originate from outside if
sound comes from nature from itself
then you
cannot move from one moment
to see a beautiful sky Then you
change to listen to a rock n
roll song like this
team I don't know that Is it okay or not
Sorry
I just heard it this morning
this song is really good about death So
what is the old panchen saying
here if this world is all natural
if the blue sky is natural and its
origin is from the sky
itself then we will never be able to
hear anything because it
will not be able to change so nature does
everything by itself it
will never change
so who is he talking about He
is talking about a
man who is very generous in
his life and makes a lot of Hai Karma
good
he has a superhero body but
he can't hear anything Why
because he doesn't come from a seed He
comes from nature
so this verse is
Indonesian we have to understand that they
are talking about nature okay
now I have another question how much
of this world comes from us
and how much comes from the
outside world we
want Billboard
09.00 DC there is a joke
that
100.0 percent
comes from ourselves
deposit episode
343 Mega absent B it gives up If
it comes from outside also the principle from
the You will not be able to move from
Zoom to rock-n-roll because there is no
reason it can move or change nature
has nothing there is no light
there is no gravity
no  there is a magnetic force it all comes
from ourselves
okay team you have the
next victim you want to tell to
read
okay
i n x factor is doing today Okay
next victim bye
image soon
is
hello hello here I continue okay okay
you
n2nedi ngeflek gangster we
creatures of pleasure staring cute
Their daughter with that version of love that
sees them so beautiful that love
will see what it sees that
does not depend on anything else as
something that really exists
direction stop appears deh something that
will never be able to change to look the
other way and that will directly
contradict the fact that when
these creatures
these creatures of pleasure fight with
their cousins ​​their feelings turn into
hatred if these creatures can
start to feel hatred then it will
contradict the idea that
their beautiful love exists in reality
and does not depend on anything else
Wow great
all of the poetry here
is
an amazing philosophy in the
old book called tab Akash sang from Pa
gillespie Nep once without Samsung eh
yes Swatch akbariza
team You have never heard of
this you remember You once asked
me
What is the spelling of
Tahta Sang meaning
theory of
searching
eh enough feat
khai one characteristic of goat peanuts story
means  if
you want the data
n to be true then there is this problem
this problem this problem this problem That's
why the whole of this poem
in English uses the word wood
or will
or gold can
because it
must be said if something is true
then there will be no affection there
will be no hatred there will be no war
if what you say is true
SDN bridgewater thesis so this
English is a bit difficult to read
because of the Tibetan language but don't
blame me because I'm not the one who
wrote the Tibetan language
they say there is a kind of
affection called ji-young jumpa which
means
a kind of affection that when you
see
something something looks very
beautiful to you
I will give you 1000 dollars
if you can
tell me where the affection
is mentioned Is it in the mantra squatting
or Oh no Is desyanti Dewa not
also
Let's just cancel the bet
Hi
mp3reggae finished pressing Tegal Menteng
there is a
cause and effect bodhicitta
warna.cat
this is one way to
develop bodhicitta
that is by feeling a
sense of
er affection like Nur loves my partner
I am very proud of
my grandson
yesterday he was the first time I saw
him walk
and pebrio I got a video about
maytri and other children
here you Try to see er
want to
try yes ichistar Walking this is
Mitra who has just started walking
and we are very happy because this
means Nur does not have to carry 30
kilos anymore
what does a mother feel about
her child why does a mother send
her grandfather
30 videos every day
that means Iyong meet that is the
love that makes her see her child
become very beautiful you are very
extraordinary the gods when they see
their child who was born in
their lap they feel love
for their child like nurmeli
Maitreya that is a very extraordinary love do
you think some percent of
that love and some percent of
their children come from
outside from nature from this direction then I
love my child so the child comes
from outside then I from within meet
my child so maytri comes
to me then I feel
love for Maitri from myself if
that is true and that is what happens
and the people we love 50% come
from outside then Okay then Samsara is a
good place for the gods there are no more
problems do you think
we have no problems do
you remember what the problem of the gods the
gods have one
problem actually or three yes they
always fight with
the  demigod because they feel
jealous then Second they
spend their seeds because they are
generous but do not know why and
third
they suffer a very
bad death when their seeds run out
then the devil is here and the
angel is here then
my head is in the middle
while gecella is trying to
think the angel and the devil are
arguing on the left and right Oh no no no where does
Maitri come from
then the angel says Oh no no no not
from my trimitra it comes
from us
then the devil says No no no
maytri comes from Maitri then the angel
says Oh if mitri really comes
from Maitri then we will never be
able to hate anything and I will not
hate eating vegetables
my wife has now given up and doesn't
want to give me vegetables anymore first she
tried to make me eat vegetables she
put them in the fridge When I didn't
eat them She threw the vegetables out
then we came to a compromise
we bought a blender
Okay I don't like vegetables but I will
put them in the blender I mix them
with honey and so on and I will
Om then my wife says Oh this is
so disgusting
So if it is true that
vegetables come from vegetables then I
will not eat donuts
If it is true that Maitri comes from mitri
then I will never be able to
hate anyone because I can't
changed because of its origin Not from me
but from them but we know that
their gods have
very bad wars
with the demigods demigod
means the
da'wah of lower
level Gods who are not as handsome
or beautiful as them So
if
this world has a natural part then
your feelings will not be able to change
from affection or love to
hate because the people you love
then the enemies who hate their origins are
from them and they will not be able to
change
now we have two changes
if your child maytri comes
from maytri
then you will not be able to listen to
him You can see him but you
will never listen to him or
feel him or touch him because
that will result in a
change from nature whereas nature is
something that is locked that
cannot change and your affection
will always be the same
in the morning there is love for him because
you wake up beside mitri and
all day long your feelings for Mitre will not change
Why Because if it is nature-nature
cannot change nature does what it
does and will not be able to change
the sky never changes the
mountains also never change
Mukhsin Zainuri next
tembereng team eh always worried must be
German post tsunami team
Okay we are in the
morning Sis exercise
Rafa
lpz Effendi spinks tulungangung when
these beings saw
their cousins ​​the creatures of almost pleasure and
began to feel in intense feelings of hatred
for them the hatred itself
began to seem as if it also existed
in reality when the war came
until finally and the creatures
of pleasure Returned to their own well list
and time also returned for
them to see the daughters of the Divine
with the thought of love seeing them
again as beauty it would
contradict the idea that
their previous hatred had ever existed
in reality and moreover if
this perception of their daughters
as beauty could start again in
their hearts Then it
would ultimately contradict the idea that
beautiful love exists in truth
once again this is very difficult Even
in English and not in English it is
also very difficult time
Hi this is what we say if this is
true then this is true Well this is true
this is very difficult to translate
because you have to really think
if
this is a bit difficult to finish Le Meme saptadewi
when we meet someone
we don't like
I used to have people in the
diamond business and I didn't like
them we had a building If I'm
not mistaken 12lt in Manhattan and I
remember when I came to work Every
morning I hoped I wouldn't
meet  with these people I think
tsunami You also feel the
same thing yes because there are also those who have worked
in big companies so you come to
a building cliff melon we pray
Oh do not want to meet this person
written When I went up to
my office there were people you do not
want to see and
excited
When you do not like
those people You have the right to feel that they
come from themselves the
reason you do not want to meet them
on the list is because you believe he
does not come from you but
they come from themselves it
turns out
they come at the same time as
you he will enter the same elevator as
you and you rice will it comes
from themselves That's why
you do not like them well
here we go deeper yes
lovebird we can talk about this
for a week but
there is a feeling of hate in
you and you feel that it
also comes from yourself
so the people who come or enter the
elevator that I do not like it
seems they come from themselves
and all the stupid things
they say to me come from
them and then I start to
dislike them I start Praying
that I will not meet
them in Life Genius then
you feel an attachment
to the feeling  hate is a feeling of
dislike
as if its origin is from outside
as if hatred originates from outside
and it doesn't change
fashion if the person
you don't like at your job
originates from themselves
and you  meet them in the
morning on the list then you will have a
feeling of hatred
all day long
even when you have come home
and you meet your child maytri
Eva
because that feeling does not come from
yourself
approach
Rizal wait there
is someone you don't like this is your
husband's wallet from inside the kitchen
who is angry with you or from where
Okay if those two things come from outside
then if I ask your thoughts
your dislike or hatred
comes from where is also called
Understand that the feeling of hatred for your husband
that you see comes from you
and your reaction your annoyance comes
from your seed
so it is very difficult to get out of
Samsara because
your natural reaction is not something
natural and comes from your seed
there are people in this universe who
When you call them stupid they
will still love you
so we have the seed to
hear your husband call you stupid
But there are also seeds that make
you angry
Kyuhyun There is a possibility that other people
will insult you but you are not
bothered and there are still happy
if it comes from yourself but if it
comes from outside then when you
come home and see their children
your children you will still hate them
like you hate your colleague who
is in the
elevator
so this is their God
at war with cousin  they are the
little gods who are always jealous of
them
if according to me that the enemies come
from outside
paint comes from myself
then I should feel hatred
When I think of them
and I will feel hatred too When
I go home and see my family
because it doesn't come from me because it does
n't come from me so
how can it change it can't
change so it's like nature
that comes from outside
then he also has satay later here
he says the hatred that
the gods feel when they fight
And when they come home
or the hatred that you feel when
you don't like someone in
your office if that person comes from
that person and not from you
then you should
bring that hatred home
if it doesn't come from yourself and
even when you can stop
that hatred there is no feeling there is no
logical reason Why can it
turn into affection When you
see Maitri there is no reason
why it can turn into love
when you go home friedrich
name hatred You will never
stop and there will still be hatred
Mitre second even if the hatred
stops you will not be able to start
loving Maitri because everything
comes from outside and not from
yourself so What is the conclusion conclusion
you can only hate someone
if it comes from you and you
can also love someone as long as it's Sri
yourself So
you make the people you
meet
very
eh this is the understanding that
[Music]
you have to understand the
width er
redcamp
ach1m
this week so I apologize if
I cough
according to my wife You can
blow your nose Hopefully on
camera but don't show the contents of the
tissue That's all You're ready
okay
setting the method of implementing the concept that
things can exist in
Hi the same as each other things in the
universe they will never exist
if one state of our mind exists
by itself then there is not a single
thing in the entire universe that
has ever appeared that can start or
stop or go or come Karma
also cannot and the consequences also
cannot Even in existence
Even in the name Okay
so don't just about so don't just
talk about the enemies of the gods and
don't just talk about
their family members they said look
maytrip is not in your life
from yourself maitrin and the
people you don't like in the
office are also not from themselves
Oh yeah forget the people you Hi
and forget the people you don't
like there is
nothing that comes
from outside the
people you like
like the children of the paladewa  it doesn't
come from themselves the
people you don't like
like demigods also don't come
from themselves
Oh yes if the people you don't
like and the people you hate
don't come from outside then there is nothing
that comes from outside
Den instant then inside this is like that
even your thoughts don't come
from your own thoughts and that's very
important yes not only that
crazy
marriage not only the people
you love like mitri come from
you not only the people you don't
like come from you Even
your reactions to those people
love and hate come from
your seed so from outside the world comes
from you nature comes from you then
your reaction to hate people
you don't like and love people
you like comes from yourself
You don't have to live like that
because everything comes from
yourself from your seed and you can
change can change your seed there are
people who don't like your country
but you can still love
them Why because your emotional reactions
come from your seed left
I
grew up in a
Christian church and there was a prayer book
and this prayer book was very beautiful and
influenced my whole life and
this is one of the
most beautiful things I have ever read
When I was young there were people who
said this was written by Shakespeare
and they studied this
church in England they studied it and
then they said Oh no it wasn't
written by a secretary written by someone
else I forgot who it was written by and then
they said this person had an
interesting life and they said Why did
they say Did you know Jesus
told people Love your
enemies as you love
your family and as you love
yourself and then a Bishop
who wrote this book he believed
it and he really wanted to
do like Jesus there was a
joke in England that said if
you don't have money
then hurt this Bishop try to
be his enemy because he really
believed in this philosophy the media will
still give you money every week
because he felt you should
treat your enemies like
your own family like
yourself so if you are lucky you
become his enemy he will still take care of
you for the rest of your life Wow this is very cool
so the natural reaction and
Hi to your enemies and to the
people who hurt us is
not natural because it can change because it
comes from your seed because this
is a seed that has been from a long time
which is caused by
misunderstanding your
reaction arises
because of
your misunderstanding of your enemies for several
lifetimes
then you can hate this person if
you are aware  that it comes from
yourself and because of
that misunderstanding then you might be
able to compete with them
kerenceng
Oh yes if your feelings can not
change then the whole world can not
change Hi and then there will be no
seeds that's how panchen lama
ended this section if your enemy
can not change and if
your feelings towards your enemy can not
change then we have to say
seeds can not work
forget about the practice of buddhism Just give up
if an enemy must be an enemy
forever
and if the person you love will
be the person you love
forever and If you react
with hatred towards your enemy and
never give
them affection Then nothing will
change then you no longer need to
practice
energy buddhism because because it can not change
when in fact Karma can change the
main faith if because it does not change then
clearly Karma does not exist
even if it comes from me
if I can not change my reaction
and If I can not change my enemy
then even cause and effect is
meaningless It does not exist
even if it comes from me if
I can not change my hatred
towards my enemy and I can not
change anything then I
can not change my seeds
even when the seeds come from
myself
the seed will not be able to change and
I will be stuck in this situation
trapped in the devil's thinking I
don't know the angel will because
maybe he will run away somewhere
okay Mister Yes
Indonesia team by lecturers I want to
announce something Cafe afraid to forget
we have 20 Man for you
Okay
this is a special project
at Diamond mountain diamond mountain
and I'm
very sad because covert in Arizona is
very the a lot so we didn't
invite anyone as a guest
this spring maybe
in the fall we will invite Yoga
they try but last November
we did a fundraiser because
we want to
replant the trees at Diamond
malten three 150 years ago cowboys
cut down most of the trees at Diamond
malten and we did a
fundraiser last November we
tried to get
Rp100 USB
to plant 3000 trees and we
managed to do it on the last day of the
retreat we got 100 thousand dollars
that was the easy part
now people have to dig
holes and put new trees
in the holes
Yoga but we are ready You can
come to Diamond mountain every year
and you can do the retreat You can
stay there I think in the month
April-May there will be a retreat
in demonteen for one month and you
can come You can scan this QR Code
and you can come and help us
to plant trees or you can
send funds to help us
plant trees Okay team there is one more these
are the new books
ndamean publishing Diamond cutter
suddenly exploded
already and there are these books namely
commentary for the Heart Sutra there is commentary
for the article
Hai Sutra Thailand cutter then
about meditation emptiness meditation
my only
and there is a
new translation
finally there is the book medicine Buddha already
medicine Okay this is a work
since the race mix naat they are now
working to translate 27
books and I must say that
we have already got the results
benoson-n Now we also have
sponsors from Austria and from Germany
who are helping the translators I
want to thank them and
I want to congratulate them because
without Project alel we would never have been
able to finish these books
make the country a
candidate for the Gold Club
I
will be Russia in Germany You are very
helpful to us and because of your help
we can translate these books I
think these books have never been
translated before they
are very profound books
all
aqamal instructions  Asyila about meditation is
in the book about meditation on emptiness
d'golden Cinere red book in
the middle of this golden key is the
best English translation book from the
main only school and comments about
Diamond cutter and nasutra be careful
Hi
You can have it And I like to
read it in the morning when I
eat breakfast I read a few
pages of the sutras The
keyboard is now all in
Ibuk form and you can scan the QR code
here and you can get the book
in just 2 minutes
because of the
hard work of Dou Chaeri's info friends
who work hard and you can
get this book
Hey girl short notice box
and this book will now be translated
into other languages ​​too
like German
eh that will not be by Sylvia
Anderson and
their work with blumenau publishers
wasted or wherever he is
now
to ISIS important much family friend the
world
Kya is printing Silvia is
printing
Abdul translated books more
than anyone in the world this book
will also come out in German and
Russian orphans any more questions
step
email Facebook only gecella business
prepare curious one of the questions
asked by some people is
when I hear all
these teachings I
became blaming myself for
everything because my bad seeds were
exposed my good seeds were exposed
my bad seeds were exposed and I always
blamed myself for this
So how do we look at it
Is there a way
We can plant seeds so that we
don't blame ourselves
that's a very good question
and
I'll
tell you the solution if
you buy the book ah
meditation by banner bopala there is
a section about the right of
low self-esteem
If you understand the first panchen lama
then you will have
very low self-esteem
because you have a high level of
confidence Rin low self-esteem
why because all the stupid things in
this world come from you and you
feel Oh my God G finished feeling
bad Before I thought it was
just my husband but it turns out
everything bad comes from
me
I know in America we are
very depressed now
thinking that we create situations
like this
so there was a discussion
in the agenda book forget
about the same question What
if I really understand that
all the bad things that happen come
from me I feel
even though it's very Hi guilty because it
all comes from me
there is a meditation technique called
cloves Sir this is
my team will give you $100 who
can  set on me What is
Singkep
Kampung SP fired
doing it
catfish streaming anu Germany veystore
fast DC Okay Okay Okay I will
give you a hint
When you feel
your mind is a bit down during
meditation How do you
raise it back up
by imagining light okay that's
one way but that's not the trigger
and good thing in your life
Okay tsunami you get $100
you have to contact Eli and say
that G Islam wants to give me $100
my ship answered the question correctly
Yes like Cisadane Okay
Idih imela Heli and send
your Paypal number Yes short Sir So that's
okay
right bicycle It's true that
stupid people in this world come
from you it's your
own fault right but
all the
beautiful stops in this world
also come from you logically like that
all the
good people all
ah charitable activities in this world every mother
who sacrifices herself for her child
all kinds of affection and love that
you see in this world all come
from yourself too So it's
true
you created
all the crazy people who like to
fight
you created them But I think there are
more good people in
this world that you created you
create
so many
billions of good people Oge who
do good things every day and
like my parents who Yours
Indonesia sacrificed their lives 20
years to raise a child in America
when a child
graduates from
University
his parents
travel go out to
celebrate
I feel it is very true
that there are more good people in
this world than bad people it's just that the
good people are not
very loud but the bad
people are
louder in fact
billions of people sacrifice themselves for
others for their families
for others they are not
published in the newspapers or in the news
but actually they exist Hi there are so many
tank tops Sir Mean wow you do
good things okay great you are
great I JG BKN Timothy we will
take a break first
There is one more question
while we listen to this
there is a debate between the devil and the Angel
in our own minds
So how can we plant the seeds
to listen more to the angel in
my mind
there is a
solution that comes to my mind
I understand the question
all day
And listen we are all the same actually the
best person in this moment and the
worst person in this room
Endless waltz the difference is only one
percent if you are in the world  This is you're
already messed up actually so don't
think about it anymore the best person
in this world and the worst person in this world are
almost the same not too much different
consistent yeah maybe only one percent
difference if you are trapped
in this world
jens So
Okay the devil will talk in
your mind all day and
you think oh can I
not listen to this
even in the book sometimes the
angel speaks but in
my mind the one who speaks the angel rarely
speaks How can I
not be a girl seen
dealing with that you know that I got
married recently and my wife
said
You are a
good speaker I love
listening to you talk
but your listening skills are not
very good slaughtered this before you die
your ears need training because you are
not very good at listening
then I have a feeling that
angels are in our minds and
are talking but we are the ones who
don't listen I feel there is in
Hi
a rule
in the universe that angels can
talk 50% then the devil can also
talk 50% but we have problems
in listening we never
listen to the angel who is
talking
and we never try to
listen to the
angel that is something we have to
practice In meditation there is a
meditation that we can do
called silent listening
in your meditation  You can try
this and
just be quiet and listen You
sit
then you
am4 posture
8.0 then instead of you bringing an object
or imagining an object in
your mind you just be quiet and listen
2.1 design on Angle Try to
listen to the angels You open
your ears wide
and listen to it become your object
this is like fixation meditation
try this is very fun
instead of you choosing an object from outside
there is just sit for 15 minutes yes also then
there is listen
and there can listen to the sound of birds the
sound of garbage trucks and things like
that and then you can also
listen to your heartbeat
Then
you can listen to the
oxygen molecules from your ears and try
to go deeper deeper even
listen again listen again and
you will start to hear
whispers from angels in
your ears but you have to be patient it can't
just be one or two days
you have to try for a week
or two weeks
cnrt and just sit meditating and just
listen
first you will hear
noisy things from outside like the sound of
dogs the sound of children
but you can go deeper and
deeper and gadgetgaul SDM in
silence just listen and
open to hear and you will
hear the voice of the
RCTI angel who will whisper Beautiful things
there are you  is a very
beautiful practice * all Okay grandpa team will make
coffee first